http://www.humaneed.com.au/privacypolicy.asp

Home | Marriage Counselling | Individual Counselling | Telephone Counselling | Locations | Contact Us
HomeAbout HumaneedWhat We OfferRelationship ArticlesF A Q 'sTestimonialsBookstoreContact UsLocationsPre Marriage Education
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is our concern.
The rules for privacy refer to personal information. Personal information is any information that can potentially identify an individual.  We only collect information required to conduct the service we provide, such as name, address, and phone contact details. Information is securely stored and full precautions are taken when information is transferred, including electronically.
We comply fully with the Federal Privacy Act and Health Records Act of Victoria. The Federal Privacy Act incorporates 10 National Privacy Principles which set out the rules for handling personal information.
FOR MORE INFORMATION
Health Services Commissioner
For general information about the Health Records Act 2001 visit the HSC website www.health.vic.gov.au/hsc
or phone 03 8601 5222
Office of the Victorian Privacy Commissioner
for general information about the Information Privacy Act 2000 visit the website http://www.privacy.vic.gov.au/
or phone 03 8619 8719
Federal Privacy Commissioner
Fro General information about the Privacy Act 1988 visit the website http://www.privacy.gov.au/
Print
Marriage Counselling Intensives | Marriage Counselling Article | Couple Counselling Melbourne | Marriage Counselling Melbourne | Marriage Counselling Sydney | Marriage Counselling Brisbane | Individual Counselling | Telephone Counselling | Locations | Contact Us | Resources | Disclaimer |
Privacy Policy | © 2005-2015 Humaneed | Created by PBSA POS
